(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
右に進むなら...
If you go right...
左の道なら...
If it's the left path...
解は？
The answer?
チャンス？
Chance?
リスクが小さい
Risk is small
右？
Right?
やっぱり右？
Right after all?
左？
Left?
どっち？
Which one?
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration
人に言えないように
So I don't say anything to anyone
愛せないように
So I cannot love
期待しないように
So I don't expect anything
孤独と過多にならないように
So I don't become too lonely
気取らぬように
So I don't act pretentious
目立たぬように
So I don't stand out
誰一人傷つけないように
So I don't hurt anyone
虐めぬように
So I don't bully
殺さぬように
So I don't kill
事欠き不全にならないように
So I don't become inadequate
威張らぬように 威張らぬように
So I don't act arrogant, so I don't act arrogant
軽いジョークや リップサービスも忘れるように
So I forget light jokes and lip service too
どんな時も笑って 愛嬌振りまくように
So I always smile and act charming
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration
とにかく言わずに ちゃんと召し上がれ
Just don't say anything and eat up
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Chocolate Decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You have to fix your pickiness
頭空っぽ そのあとに
With an empty head, after that
残る心が本物なら
If the heart that remains is real
きっと君だって同じこと
Surely you're the same way
ところで一つ伺いますが
By the way, let me ask you one thing
現実は...
Reality is...
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
もっと日常を抑えられるように
So I can suppress my daily life more
鼻垂れるように
As if my nose is running
分かれるように
As if separating
ガム噛んだ口を閉ざさぬように
So as not to close my mouth while chewing gum
笑わすように
To make others laugh
笑われるように
To be laughed at
人ちゃんと敬うように
To respect people properly
崇めるように
To revere them
讃えるように
To praise them
有象無象にならないように
So as not to become part of the masses
ふざけないように
So as not to mess around
集団さんから終止形まで
From the 'Shuudan' group to the final form
へいこれへいこれ言っちゃって
Saying "Hey, this, hey, this"
あれ前髪超絶最強じゃん
Look, my bangs are absolutely the best, right?
とかどうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Saying things that don't even matter
毎晩毎晩もう限界
Every night, every night, I'm at my limit
宗教的社会の終端です
It's the end of a religious society
決して発狂しないように
So as never to go insane
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
Sometimes, lonely love stains you
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
兎角の後にひと言の愛
After all is said and done, one word of love
始めはあなた言ったそうな
At first, you seemed to have said it
大言壮語の並べた語
Words arranged in grandiloquence
いえいえいやいや好きな文字
No, no, no, no, favorite words
いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
My, my, but this is the first time today
こんなトコまで君センスあるよ
You've got style, even in a place like this
恋すべき季節にビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration in the season for love
恋すべき気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration with feelings of love
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Yearning for the ideal everyone wants
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
個性や情を全部焼き払い
Burning away all individuality and emotion
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Killing greed and ego and burying them in the dirt
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
僕は大人にやっと成ったよママ
I've finally become an adult, Mama
明日もきっとこの先も
Surely tomorrow, and from now on too
地獄は続くどこまでも
Hell will continue, forever and ever
あだおろそか今だけも
Even just for now, don't take it lightly
本当の心の気持ちのままで
While staying true to your real feelings
必死まじになってやってこうぜ
Let's give it our absolute all
ああ思い出した朝あの時の生真面目さ
Ah, I remembered that morning, the seriousness of that time
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
サイコロ...
Dice...
5が出た
A five came out
ん？何これ？
Huh? What's this?
椅子？
Chair?
One, two, one, two...
Deal with the devil
ああ札束は世の常
Ah, wads of cash are the way of the world
狂うた者こそ勝者
Those who go mad are the winners
肝心なのは其の眼
What's important is those eyes
出し抜いてサバイヴ
Outwit and survive
行き着く先にはヘル・オア・ヘヴン
At the end of the line, it's Hell or Heaven
この世界（ルール）は
This world (rule) is
たったひとり勝者こそ正義
Only the sole winner is justice
女は度胸を散らして見せるのあいつは
She shows off her courage, that girl
やれることなんだってやるあたしは
I'll do whatever it takes, for I am
賭け狂いのクィーン
The Kakegurui Queen
お見通しよ強情
I've seen through your stubbornness
弱気手出しは無用だわ
No need for half-hearted interference
欲しがりねお上手
How greedy, and how clever
ダイヤモンド負けない輝かせてろよ様に
A diamond that won't lose, keep it shining as it should
あなた内緒だわ
It's a secret between us
...見せてあげる
...I'll show you.
秘密って甘い毒
Secrets are a sweet poison.
仕掛けて 罠にハメるわ
Setting them up, I'll trap them in my snare.
指先 誘ううなじよ
My fingertips, your inviting nape.
心は求めてる じれったい
My heart is yearning, it's so frustrating.
何も知らないような顔で
With a face that looks like it knows nothing,
踊るわ あなたを
I'll dance you around.
かすり傷に 油断見せ 読み切ったレシオだ
Showing my guard is down for a scratch,
I've read the ratio.
目移りだって 変に逃さないわ
Even as your eyes wander,
I won't let a strange one slip away.
どんな小さなズレだってお見通しの目は ごまかされないわ
Even the smallest deviation, my seeing eyes
won't be fooled.
I'm the gambler 愛だとかレース ギャンブル相手はごめんだわ
I'm the gambler, love or races,
I don't want a gambling partner.
失格してあげる
I'll disqualify you.
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let my targeted prey escape.
唇 濡らして 頂くわ もう一度
Wetting my lips, I'll have you once more.
ダイヤのジャックで 手が揃うわ
With a Jack of Diamonds, my hand is complete.
笑みは殺し待つだけ
I'll just kill my smile and wait.
私のポーカーフェイスはパーフェクト
My poker face is perfect.
一部の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show even the slightest opening.
Don't think about what comes after one game.
視線感じて上から
I feel your gaze from above.
お熱いのは 最後まで
Stay hot until the very end.
見てばかりいないで アタシが 欲しいなら
Don't just watch, if you want me.
負けるのは怖い? 合図して 読み切ったレシオだ
Scared to lose? Give the signal, I've read the ratio.
目移りだって変にかわして アタシのものにする あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Dodge those wandering eyes and make you mine,
every last strand of your hair.
I'm the gambler 愛だとかレース 震えているのよ 坊や どこまで行くの?
I'm the gambler, love or races,
you're trembling, boy, how far will you go?
目移りだって 手を貸すわ 躊躇い忘れ 誰にも触らせない このままで
Even for wandering eyes, I'll lend a hand,
forget hesitation, I won't let anyone touch you,
just like this.
I'm the gambler 愛だとかレース さぁ覚悟決めて 灰になるまで打って
I'm the gambler, love or races,
now prepare yourself, keep playing until you turn to ash.
欲しがる気持ちはまだ ベビー
Your greedy feelings are still baby-like.
誰にも負けない感じさせて ダーリン
Make me feel like I won't lose to anyone, Darling.
あれ? 椅子なくなっちゃった...
Wait? The chairs are gone...
あぁ...もうちょっと座らせて欲しかった...
Ahh... I wanted to sit for a bit longer...
はい! みんな見えてる? 聞こえてる?
Alright! Can everyone see me? Can you hear me?
ホロライブ所属の癒し系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです!
I'm the healing-type half-elf from Hololive,
Aki Rosenthal, also known as AkiRose!
ハロハロハロ! アローナ!
Halo-halo-halo! Aloha!
はぁ...えー、今回のアキロゼ生誕祭2026へ、ようこそ!
Whew... Uh, welcome to AkiRose Birthday 2026!
早速ね、なんか色々行われていたんですが、
Right away, there's been various things going on, but...
一体今回のライブはどうなっちゃうのか、是非最後まで一瞬、
just what will happen in this live? Please,
for every single moment until the end,
お見逃しなくお願いします!
don't miss a thing!
今回のライブのハッシュタグは、「#アキロゼ生誕祭2026」。
The hashtag for this live is "#アキロゼ生誕祭2026".
こちらをつけて、Xにたくさんポストしてね!
Add this and post lots on X!
もちろん、可愛いスクショ...フゥー!
Of course, cute screenshots... whew!
良いのたくさん撮って、合わせてポストしてください。
Take lots of good ones and post them together.
ライブが終わった後、アキロゼ見に行きます! 見てね!
After the live, I'll go check them out! Watch till the end!
あ、チャンネル登録もよろしくね! オッケー?
Oh, and please subscribe to the channel! Okay?
ポチッとな。はい、ありがとう!
Click. Yes, thank you!
うーん...っていうか、ここどこなんだろう? うーん...
Hmm... I mean, where am I exactly? Hmm...
おっ? おおー! あんな所にルーレットがある!
Oh? Whoa! There's a roulette wheel over there!
え、回るのかな?
Huh, I wonder if it spins?
おっ、回ったー! え、すごーい!
Oh, it's spinning! Whoa, amazing!
おー、回った! 何が出るかな?
Oh, it spun! I wonder what'll come up?
何が出るんだろう？
What will come out?
お！え？お？え？
Oh! Eh? Oh? Eh?
何、何、何？どうなっちゃうの？
What, what, what? What's going to happen?
ピース？
Peace?
ん？何だ？
Hmm? What is it?
Ah Happy なけなしの情
Ah Happy, the meager passion
Unlucky どなた様も
Unlucky, everyone
Be Happy いま目醒めせよ
Be Happy, wake up now
Undead 生きているんだろ
Undead, you're alive, right?
目を逸らした過去も
The past you turned away from
退屈な未来も
The tedious future too
カウントダウン 嗚呼 やれやれ
Countdown, ah, good grief
古今東西 ピース ピース
All times and places, peace, peace
UNDEAD
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
ねえねえねえ なんだかどうして
戦ってるようなそんな気がするの
Hey, hey, hey, for some reason
I feel like I'm fighting
逃げられない 痛くもない ここにいる自分
Can't run, doesn't hurt, my self who's right here
とっくに死んでる 透明なブレイド対決
Long since dead, a duel with transparent blades
痛いけどいたい記憶の奥
Deep inside the memories I want to keep, even though they hurt
残念 もういないのに あれ そっちがアイロニー
Too bad, I'm not here anymore,
oh, that's the irony
透かされてるのは今の自分
The one being seen through is my current self
ナンセンス 消えないレッテル 言わばコンプレックス
Nonsense, an indelible label,
so to speak, a complex
取り憑かれてるみたい 巻きついたまま
It's like being possessed, remaining entwined
まだ離れない 有りし日の自分
My self from former days still won't leave
Undead
死んじゃいない お前とお前の連鎖
Not dead, the chain between you and yourself
生きてるかどう問われ続けるカタチ
A form that continues to be asked if it's alive
不相応に甘んじて満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied with settling for less than you deserve
幸せになろうとしないなんて 酷だ
It's cruel not to even try to be happy
この世 この世は奇怪奇怪ファンタジー
This world, this world is a strange, strange fantasy
次は鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
Will a demon appear next, or a snake?
待って待って やっと始まる物語
Wait, wait, the story is finally beginning
さあ行こうぜ 化け物ばかりの その舞台 ピース ピース
Let's go, that stage full of nothing but monsters,
peace, peace
Ah... The future can't change the past...
But the future is now for the future...
ねえなんだかどうして 未来になんてさほどの
Hey, for some reason,
for the future, not much...
期待も持てないような気がして
I feel like I can't hold much expectation
もう随分生きてる 意趣返し テンプレ 食傷
I've lived long enough, revenge, templates, fed up
素敵なんて出来事の気配もない
Not even a hint of something wonderful happening
残念 既出経験 因果形骸化
Too bad, already experienced,
causality reduced to a shell
私は退屈の進化
I am the evolution of boredom
今日は刺激が欲しいんだ 飽きちゃった誰かさん
I want some excitement today,
someone who's gotten bored
なんて悟って浮かべる セルフコンプライアンス
Realizing that, I display self-compliance
透かされていくみたい 垂直降下
It's like being seen through, a vertical drop
あれもこれもどれも同じ味がする
This, that, and everything tastes the same
Undead
死んじゃいない お前とお前の連鎖
Not dead, the chain between you and yourself
いつの世も過去も未来も今にあるんだ
In any age, the past and future are in the present
生きていることを愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill the act of living with simple honesty
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending
Undead
死んじゃいない お前に見せてるんだ
Not dead, I'm showing you
幸せを諦めてしまうな 人であれ
Don't give up on happiness, be human
ただ苦しみに慣れて耐えているだけじゃ
If you're just used to suffering and enduring it...
死んでいるも同然 屍の Undead
You're as good as dead, a corpse of an Undead
Ah Happy なけなしの情
Ah Happy, the meager passion
Unlucky どなた様も
Unlucky, everyone
Be Happy いま目醒めせよ
Be Happy, wake up now
生きているんだろう
You're alive, aren't you?
不相応に足掻け 幸せに成るの
Struggle for what you don't deserve,
to become happy
もう全部全部お前だ 古今東西
It's all you, all of it, all times and places
死ぬまで遊べ ピース ピース
Play until you die, peace, peace
Ah... The future can't change the past...
But the future is now for the future...
独りになれど怖くはないこと
That you're not afraid even if you become alone
この化け物ばかりの 舞台 ピース ピース
This stage full of nothing but monsters,
peace, peace
愛♡スクリーム！
作詞：aim
作曲：DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
Ai Scream!
Lyrics: aim
Composition: DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai Scream!
教えてもっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about yourself
Tell me more & more, Tell me more & more
聞かせてもっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice
Let me know more & more, Let me know more & more
こんなドキドキ 想像できない
I can't imagine this kind of excitement
Oh I need you, Oh I need you
友達は卒業 運命の私
Graduating from being friends, find my destined self
見つけてほしいな
I want you to find me
Fu!
勇気を出して
Have courage
見つめる作戦
Staring strategy
緊張がいっぱい
Full of tension
止まれない
Can't stop
Yeah Yeah Yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this love, with this affection
Ne Ne Ne
Hey, hey, hey
とろけちゃうよ
I'm melting
Ne Ne Ne
Hey, hey, hey
気づいて My Darling
Notice me, my darling
届け 大好き
Reach out, I love you
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
はじめちゃん！
Hajime-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミントより も・あ・な・た！
More than choco mint... it's YOU!
リリカちゃん！
Ririka-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
シトラスベリーフレーバーより も・あ・な・た！
More than citrus berry flavor... it's YOU!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームより も・あ・な・た！
More than cookie & cream... it's YOU!
みんな！
Everyone!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き アイスクリーム！
Of course we love ice cream!
止まれない Yeah Yeah Yeah
Can't stop, yeah, yeah, yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this love, with this affection
Ne Ne Ne とろけちゃうよ
Hey, hey, hey, I'm melting
Ne Ne Ne 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
溶けちゃう 大好き
I'm melting, I love you
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
お願い 見つけて My Darling
Please find me, my darling
お願い 気づいて My Darling
Please notice me, my darling
勇気を出して
Have courage
近づく作戦
Closing in strategy
緊張が増えて
Tension is building
止まれない Yeah Yeah Yeah
Can't stop, yeah, yeah, yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this love, with this affection
Ne Ne Ne とろけちゃうよ
Hey, hey, hey, I'm melting
Ne Ne Ne 気づいて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
それは あなた
It is you
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
愛 愛 スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, scream, let's shout
スクリーム 愛 スクリーム
Scream, love, scream
あ、元気もらえて面白くてオレンジでシャンパンコール得意な人いないかな？
Oh, is there anyone who can give me energy, who's funny and in orange, and good at champagne calls?
それ俺やないかい！
That's me, isn't it!
ちょっといいから見せてくれないか？
Wait a sec, won't you show me?
お前のセクシー・フェロモンで俺メロメロ
Your sexy pheromones make me head over heels
詰めちゃいそうでもいけないの
Seems like I'm closing in, but I can't
高鳴る鼓動止められないわ
This racing heartbeat won't stop
交わす言葉の記憶遠く
Memories of exchanged words are far away
口元 動きに揺れ動く
Lips swaying with the movements
...濡れた髪を撫でた そして Ah Ah Ah
...Stroked the wet hair, and then Ah Ah Ah
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC won't continue, isn't that just no good?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep in your heart, it's different, isn't it?
俺の青春 そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to reach the end in the heat
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's got to be you or I don't want it
俺はイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
Na na na...
赤い糸なんて嘘っぱち
The red thread of fate is just a lie
でもしたごころでさえ信じたいな
But I want to believe even in ulterior motives
俺は正しい 君も正しい
I'm right, you're right
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
Anyway, I won't be swayed anymore
騙し騙され胸を突くような
Deceiving and being deceived, like a piercing in the chest
芝居がより盛り上げるよ
The acting makes it more exciting
息が耳に触れた二人 Ah Ah Ah
Breaths touched our ears, the two of us Ah Ah Ah
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC won't continue, isn't that just no good?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep in your heart, it's different, isn't it?
私の青春 そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to reach the end in the heat
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's got to be you or I don't want it
私イケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
交わす言葉の記憶と口元の動きにギュッとなる
The memories of exchanged words and the movement of your mouth make me tight
濡れた髪を撫でた そして Ah Ah Ah
Stroked the wet hair, and then Ah Ah Ah
ABC
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC won't continue, isn't that just no good?
だって心の奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep in your heart, it's different, isn't it?
俺たちの青春 そんなもんじゃない
Our youth isn't something like that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
We want to reach the end in the heat
きっと君じゃなきゃやだよ
It's got to be you or I don't want it
俺はイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
絡み合う糸は君と
The intertwining threads are with you
俺を結ぶ赤い糸
The red thread connecting me
（はあ…はあ…）
(Pant... pant...)
みんな... 来てくれて
Everyone... for coming
ありがとう！
thank you!
ということで、お友達が来てくれたので
And so, since my friends are here
せっかくなので自己紹介してもらおうと思います！
I'm going to have them introduce themselves!
まずはぷるるんから！
First off, from Pururun!
はーい！おはぷれ！
Hi! Ohapure!
天使と悪魔のぷるぷるエンジェルデビル、甘塚ぷるるです！
Half angel, half devil, Puru Puru Angel Devil, Amatsuka Pururu!
あきろぜちゃ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Akiroze-cha, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやあ、とっても楽しかったです！
Man, it was so much fun!
ありがとう！最高！
Thank you! Supreme!
そして続いてかるびちゃ！
And next, Karubi-cha!
はい、お肉の国のお姫様、赤見かるびです！
Hi, Princess of the Meat Country, Akami Karubi!
あきろぜ、誕生日おめでとう！
Akiroze, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやライブって、お友達とライブ初めてだからさ
You know, a live performance, it's my first live with friends
まじで嬉しかったよ
so I was really happy.
本当？
Really?
ありがと呼んでくれて
Thanks for inviting me.
またやろうね！
Let's do it again!
また！
Again!
はーい！ありがとう！
Hi! Thank you!
素晴らしい！そして最後に
Wonderful! And finally
ずずさん！
Zuzu-san!
はい！僕のこと知らない人いると思うんで自己紹介だけさせてください！
Hi! I think there are people who don't know me, so let me just introduce myself!
雨降ってザーザー 諸々事態はジージー
Rain falling za-za, various situations are ji-ji
俺の名前はずずずずずず、ずずでございます！
My name is Zu-zu-zu-zu-zu-zu, it's Zuzuzu!
いやあ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Man, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
（笑い）疲れた
(Laughs) Tired
お忙しい人気者だ
The busy popular one is here!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう、みこち、そらちゃん、ありがとう！
Thank you Miko-chi, Sora-chan, thank you!
ああ、賑やかで楽しかった
Ah, that was so lively and fun.
JANE DOE
作詞・作曲：米津玄師
Lyrics & Composition: Kenshi Yonezu
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world
二人だけみたいだね
it's only the two of us.
なんて少しだけ
Just for a moment,
夢を見てしまっただけ
I was just dreaming.
爪先に月明かり
Moonlight on my toes,
花束の香り
the scent of a bouquet,
指に触れる指
fingers touching fingers.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I have to go now,
何もかも忘れて
forgetting everything.
ガラスの上を
Walking barefoot
裸足のまま歩く
on top of glass.
痛むごとに
With every pain,
血が流れて 堕ちていく
blood flows and I fall.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints
会いに来て
and come see me.
錆びたプールに 放たれていく金魚
Goldfish being released into a rusty pool.
靴箱の中に 隠した林檎
An apple hidden inside a shoebox.
萎びた君の肌に ぬかるむ傷跡
Muddy scars on your withered skin,
犬のように泳いだ迷い子
a lost child who swam like a dog.
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
どこにいるよ
I'm right here.
何をしてるの？
What are you doing?
何も見てるよ
I'm watching everything.
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
そばにいたよ
I was by your side.
遊びに行こうよ
Let's go play.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を
Walking barefoot
裸足のまま歩く
on top of glass.
痛むごとに
With every pain,
血が流れて 堕ちていく
blood flows and I fall.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints
会いに来て
and come see me.
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world
二人だけみたいだね
it's only the two of us.
なんて少しだけ
Just for a moment,
夢を見てしまっただけ
I was just dreaming.
さあ、選択の時だ
Now, it's time to choose.
コイン
Coin.
このコインは…
This coin is...
はは。そうか。君はそっちなんだね。
Haha. I see. You're on that side, then.
そっち？
That side?
ここに座って。
Sit here.
え…
Uh...
この後は…君次第だよ。
After this... it's up to you.
Whisper Whisper Whisper
作詞・作曲：Azari
Lyrics & Composition: Azari
忘れられないのはこの目のせい
The reason I can't forget is because of these eyes
赤く残る過ち　甘噛みの跡
Errors remaining in red, marks of a light bite
零れ出した飢えは止めどない
The overflowing hunger is relentless
誰もいない間に悪魔を探す
Searching for the devil while no one is around
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is because of these ears
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling out from within deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper　まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して悪魔を駆ける
Escaping this cage and running with the devil
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
A night where even the words I want to say are bitten back
Whisper Whisper Whisper　まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't reveal it yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God and spending time with the devil
曖昧に夢見ていたいあなたに
To you who wants to dream vaguely
そっと気づかせてあげたいだけ
I just want to gently make you notice
おおあなたにも　おおあなたにも　おおあなたにも
Oh, to you too... oh, to you too... oh, to you too...
消えない傷を隠したいあなたに
To you who wants to hide wounds that won't fade
そっと悩ませてあげたいだけ
I just want to gently make you worry
おおあなたにも　おおあなたにも　悪魔を探す
Oh, to you too... oh, to you too... searching for the devil
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is because of these ears
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling out from within deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper　まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して悪魔を駆ける
Escaping this cage and running with the devil
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
A night where even the words I want to say are bitten back
Whisper Whisper Whisper　まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't reveal it yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God and spending time with the devil
BANG!!!
作詞：ryo (supercell) 作曲：Giga
Lyrics: ryo (supercell) Composition: Giga
好き嫌い常識 I don't care ぶっ飛べバーン！
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, blast off, BANG!
高値買い majority 私に負けはなし
Buying at a high price, majority, I never lose
ここまでって引かれた　そのボーダー誰のルール？
The border drawn saying "this far"... whose rule is that?
あの日乗り越えた weak point
The weak point I overcame that day
強くなった私が笑い飛ばしてあげる
The now-stronger me will laugh it off for you
言いたいことは言う
I say what I want to say
やりたくないことはしない
I don't do what I don't want to do
悪意気にしない
I don't care about malice
みんな違うの当然だし
It's natural for everyone to be different
私も変わんない　目の前の自分
I won't change either, the self right in front of me
Everybody say “I want to be free”
お裾分けはいいな　それじゃ何も変えられんな
Hand-me-downs are nice, but you can't change anything like that
Everybody say “I want some more”
構わない自分肯定　生きてるんだ私
Self-affirmation is fine, I'm living my life
ねえ生きてるんだ私
Hey, I'm living my life
壊れそう…
Feels like breaking...
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ
I've been choosing ever since I was born
思い出せ　私は私だ
Remember, I am myself
愚かな事など　何一つもない　嘘じゃない
There's nothing foolish about it, it's not a lie
なりたい自分に
Into the self I want to be
好き嫌い常識 I don't care ぶっ飛べバーン！
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, blast off, BANG!
振る手ならさ　てかこのリリック増さ
If it's a waving hand... well, this lyric will increase
分からす　挑発　下向いて舌打ちからのハイ！
Make them understand, provocation, look down, click your tongue, then "Hi!"
Excuse me?　力ずくハイ！
Excuse me? With all my might, hi!
優しく来なよ
Come at me gently.
パンチライン聴かせてあげる あぁ
I'll let you hear the punchline, ah.
やってから考えな
Think about it after you do it.
私が付いているから あぁ
Because I'm here with you, ah.
Everybody say I want to be free
食らうこのビート吸収 全部黙らす
Absorb this beat you take, silence them all.
目覚ませ 起きろ Wake up Wake up
Awaken, get up, wake up, wake up.
生きてる私
I am alive.
ねぇ 生きてる私
Hey, I am alive.
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ 思い出せ
I've been choosing since the moment I was born, remember it.
私は私だ
I am myself.
不可能なことなど何一つもないさ そうじゃないと
There's not a single impossible thing, that's how it is.
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ 思い出せ
You've been choosing since the moment you were born, remember it.
あなたはあなただ
You are yourself.
不可能なことなど何一つもないさ そうじゃないの
There's not a single impossible thing, isn't that right?
なりたい自分に
To the self you want to be.
Against 好き嫌い正直 I don't care フットペダル
Against likes and dislikes, honestly I don't care, foot pedal.
Bad Apple!!
作曲:Haruka 作詞:ZUN
Composed by Haruka, Lyrics by ZUN
流れてく時の中ででも けだるさが
Even in the flowing time, a listlessness...
ほらグルグル回って 私から離れる
...is spinning around and around, leaving me.
心も見えないわ そう知らない
I can't even see my heart, I just don't know.
自分から動くこともなく 時の隙間に
Without even moving on my own, in the gaps of time...
流され続けて 知らないわ
...I continue to be swept away, I don't know.
周りのことなど 私は私 それだけ
The things around me, I am just myself, that's all.
夢見てる なにも見てない 語るも無駄な
I'm dreaming, I'm seeing nothing, it's useless to speak...
自分の言葉を
...of my own words.
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ なにも感じず
Being sad is just tiring, without feeling anything...
過ごせばいいの
...I should just pass the time.
戸惑う言葉 与えられても 自分の心
Even if I'm given confusing words, my own heart...
ただ上の空
...is just absent-minded.
もし私から動くのならば すべて変えるの
If I were to move on my own, I'd change everything...
なら黒にする
...then I'll make it black.
こんな自分に未来はあるの こんな世界に
Is there a future for a self like this? In a world like this...
私はいるの
...do I exist?
今切ないの 今悲しいの 自分のことも
Now it's painful, now it's sad, even about myself...
わからないまま
...remaining unknown.
歩むことさえ疲れるだけよ 人のことなど
Even walking is just tiring, other people's business...
知りもしないわ
...I don't even know about.
こんな私も変われるのなら もし変われるのなら
If even someone like me can change, if I can change...
白になる
...I'll become white.
流れてく時の中ででも けだるさが
Even in the flowing time, a listlessness...
ほらグルグル回って 私から離れる
...is spinning around and around, leaving me.
心も見えないわ そう知らない
I can't even see my heart, I just don't know.
自分から動くこともなく 時の隙間に
Without even moving on my own, in the gaps of time...
流され続けて 知らないわ
...I continue to be swept away, I don't know.
周りのことなど 私は私 それだけ
The things around me, I am just myself, that's all.
夢見てる なにも見てない 語るも無駄な
I'm dreaming, I'm seeing nothing, it's useless to speak...
自分の言葉を
...of my own words.
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ
Being sad is just tiring.
逃げよう
I'll run away
何も感じず 過ごせばいいの
I should just spend my time feeling nothing
戸惑う言葉 与えられても
Even if I'm given bewildering words
自分の心 ただ上の空
My heart is just wandering elsewhere
もし私から 動くのならば
If I were to make a move
すべて変えるのなら 黒にする
If I were to change everything, I'd make it black
動くのならば
If I were to move
すべて壊すわ
I'll destroy everything
悲しむならば
If I were to grieve
私の心 白く変われる？
Can my heart turn white?
あなたのことも 私のことも
About you, about me
すべてのことも まだ知らないの
About everything, I still don't know
重い瞼を 開けたのならば
If I were to open these heavy eyelids
すべて壊すのなら 黒になれ
If I'm to destroy everything, let it be black
Magia
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
One day, the light of love you light in your eyes
時を越えて
Will cross through time
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を 確かに一つ
And surely destroy one of the dreams...
壊すだろう
...of this world rushing toward destruction
躊躇いを飲み干して
Drink down your hesitation
君が望むものは何？
What is it that you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
In the destination of such greedy longings
儚い明日はあるの？
Is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic...
古の魔法のように
...I used to dream of as a child
闇さえ砕く力で
With power that can even shatter darkness
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet you smiling
震えるこの手の中には
In these trembling hands...
手折られた花の勇気
...lies the courage of a plucked flower
想いだけが頼るすべて
Our feelings are all we can rely on
光を呼び覚ます願い
A wish that awakens the light
いつか君も誰かのために
One day, you too will probably...
強い力を望むのだろう
...desire great power for someone's sake
愛が胸を捕らえた夜に
On a night when love captures your heart
未知の言葉が生まれて来る
Unknown words will be born
迷わずに行けるのなら
If I can go without hesitation
心が砕けてもいいわ
It's fine if my heart breaks
いつも目の前の悲しみに
I want a spell to stand against...
立ち向かうための呪文が欲しい
...the sadness always before my eyes
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are still a dreaming memory
私は眠らない明日
I am a sleepless tomorrow
二人が出会う奇跡を
To seize the miracle...
勝ち取るために進むわ
...of our encounter, I move forward
怯えるこの手の中には
In these frightened hands...
手折られた花の刃
...lies the blade of a plucked flower
想いだけが生きるすべて
Our feelings are all we live for
心に振りかざす願い
A wish brandished within the heart
とらわれた太陽の輝く
The radiance of a captive sun
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
Back when I loved books about Wonderland
願いはきっと叶うと教えるお伽話を信じた
I believed in fairy tales that taught me wishes would surely come true
光と影の中...
Amidst the light and shadow...
静かに咲き乱れていた古の魔法をやさしく
Gently, the ancient magic that was quietly blooming in profusion
世界を変える力がその手にあると囁く
Whispers that the power to change the world is in those hands
終わらない夢を見よう君と行く時の中で
Let's dream a never-ending dream within the time I spend with you
思いだけが生きるすべて命を作るのは願い
Thoughts are everything to live for; it's a wish that creates life
わあー！
Wahhh!
アキちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Aki-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとう！イエーイ！
Thank you! Yay!
いやあ、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます。
Wow, thank you for coming today.
いえいえ、こちらこそですよ。呼んでくれてありがとうございます。
No, no, the pleasure is ours. Thanks for inviting us.
実はね、二人を呼んだのちょっと理由があって。
Actually, there's a reason I invited you two.
お？何だ何だ？
Oh? What is it?
前に、アキロゼの4周年の時に、
Before, during Akirose's 4th anniversary,
三人でKalafinaさんの曲出させてもらったんだけど。
the three of us performed a Kalafina song.
やりましたね。めっちゃ良かったやつね！
We did. That was such a good one!
そう、ハーモニーがね、そう。わあ。
Right, the harmony. Yeah. Wow.
もうね、ミオちゃんの歌も大好きだし、
I really love Mio-chan's singing,
あずさの歌も大好きだし、もうね、忘れられないの。
and I love Azusa's singing too. I can't forget it.
忘れられない！分かる、分かる！
Can't forget it! I get it, I get it!
そう！だから、もう一回、
Right! So, once more,
このライブステージで三人で歌いたくて、今日は来てもらいました。
I wanted to sing as a trio on this live stage, so I asked you here today.
嬉しい！ありがと、ありがと！
I'm so happy! Thank you, thank you!
そう、だから、まあこれから、これを機に、
Right, so from now on, taking this opportunity,
もっと何か三人で歌ったりとか、何かそういうの挑戦できたらめっちゃ嬉しい。
I'd be so happy if we could try singing together more as three or things like that.
いいですか？ハーモニーを重ねていきましょうよ。
Is it okay? Let's keep layering those harmonies.
え、いいの？嬉しい！
Eh, is it okay? I'm so happy!
何か、何かユニット名とか欲しいな。
I want... I want a unit name or something.
ね。何だろうね。え、何かちょっと世界目指せるぐらいのさ、
Right. What would it be? I want something that can aim for the world,
ユニットにしてさ、世界。世界の、世界のコンサートしようよ！
a unit like that. The world. Let's do a world concert!
したいね！したいね！世界に轟く、我らの...
I want to! I want to! Something that resonates with the world, our...
何かをね、したいということで、この三人でライブとか、アコースティックとか、
I want to do something, like a live show with the three of us, or acoustic,
何かオーケストラライブとか。わあ！良くないですか？
maybe an orchestral live. Wow! Doesn't that sound great?
そんなことをしてみたい。ねえ。我らならできるかもしれない！
I'd love to try that. Yeah. We might be able to do it!
やばいよ！お願いできる、お願いします。お願いします。
That's crazy! Can I count on you? Please. Please.
あれ？え？これは一体何ですか？
Wait? Eh? What on earth is this?
もしかして、このライブでみんなからの、
Could it be, from everyone at this live,
何か良いパワーで。何か良いパワー来てる！スピリチュアルじゃん、それ！
some good power. Some good power is coming! That's spiritual!
何だよ、そのパワー。こちらが何と完成しました！
What's that power? This has somehow been completed!
わあー！何だそれー！
Wahhh! What is that!
実は。お！
Actually... Oh!
この後、アキロゼの新曲が出ます！
After this, Akirose's new song will be out!
わあー！出たー！出たー！
Wahhh! It's out! It's here!
こちら、まあ今回、あのライブの、テーマというか、
This is, well, the theme of this live, or rather,
壮大ななテーマがあるんですけど、おお。
it has a grand theme. Ohhh.
そちらを、まあ詰まったような楽曲になってます。
It's a song that's packed with all of that.
そして、ライブ終わりの日付が変わる時に、リリースしますので、
And it will be released when the date changes after the live ends,
ぜひ買って、聞いてください！いいですね、みんな聞こうぜ！
so please buy it and listen to it! Nice, let's all listen!
ではではでは、じゃあ次の曲に行きますか。
Now then, shall we move on to the next song?
次の曲？え？
Next song? Eh?
新曲お披露目、しちゃいます！
The new song reveal... I'm going to do it!
お新曲お披露目？え、今からってこと？
New song reveal? Eh, you mean starting now?
今から頑張ります！もう最後まで見逃せないですね！
Starting now, I'll do my best! You can't miss it until the very end!
楽しみだ！お願いします。あきちゃん、頑張ってね！
I'm looking forward to it! Good luck, Aki-chan!
ありがとう！またね！頑張れ頑張れ！頑張るよー！
Thank you! See you! Good luck! I'll do my best!
モノポリー
Monopoly
魅惑の言葉の裏面に忍ばせた
Embedded on the flip side of captivating words
1mgのスパイス
1mg of spice
たちまち華麗な指先で彩る
Instantly coloring with magnificent fingertips
本日のダイス
Today's dice
当たり前だって恐縮してちゃ
If you're too humble to accept it's only natural
生き残れないでしょう
You won't survive, will you?
率直に言って その全てが欲しい
To be honest, I want it all
一人勝ちにオールイン
All in on a solo win
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, right?
翻弄して 翻弄されて ゾクゾク
Toying around, being toyed with, I'm shivering
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょ
Even if you take a hit, it's what you wanted, right?
最低だって化けるでしょ
Even the lowest can transform, right?
見透かして 見透かされて 故に終わりはない
Seeing through, being seen through, therefore there is no end
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
All of this thumping heart is non-fiction
嗜むはずでも たまには飲みすぎて
Even if I only meant to enjoy a bit, sometimes I drink too much
一回休み
One turn skip
周りもざわつく 思わぬうたた寝で
The surroundings are also buzzing from an unexpected nap
二回休み
Two turns skip
切れる頭と勘だけじゃ
Something that can't be obtained
手に入らないモノ
just with a sharp mind and intuition
そこで一打 見越されるならいい
One stroke there, if it's anticipated, that's fine
命懸けで楽しむわ
I'll enjoy it with my life on the line
天と地は案外近くない？ この通り命懸け
Aren't heaven and earth unexpectedly close? Just like this, life on the line
たかがモノポリー されど大勝負
It's just Monopoly, but it's a big gamble
決める 想いで今宵の 私は強い
Deciding with these feelings, tonight I am strong
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, right?
翻弄して 翻弄されて ゾクゾク
Toying around, being toyed with, I'm shivering
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょ
Even if you take a hit, it's what you wanted, right?
最低だって化けるでしょ
Even the lowest can transform, right?
見透かして 見透かされて 故に終わりはない
Seeing through, being seen through, therefore there is no end
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
All of this thumping heart is non-fiction
堕ちても 昇っても ノンフィクション
Whether falling or rising, it's non-fiction
葛飾ラプソディー
Katsushika Rhapsody
中川に浮かぶ 夕陽をめがけて
Aiming for the setting sun floating in the Nakagawa River
小石を蹴ったら 靴まで飛んで
When I kicked a pebble, even my shoe flew off
ジョギングしていた 大工の頭に
And hit the master carpenter who was jogging
ガキのままだと 笑われたのさ
I was laughed at, told I'm still a kid
どこかに元気を 落っことしても 葛飾亀有
Even if you drop your energy somewhere, Katsushika Kameari
あくびをひとつ 変わらない街並みが 妙に優しいよ
With a yawn, the unchanging cityscape is strangely kind
中央広場で 子供の手を引く
In the central plaza, leading a child by the hand
太ったあの娘は 初恋の人
That girl who got plump was my first love
ゴンパチ池で 渡したラブレター
The love letter I gave her at Gonpachi Pond
今も持ってる と からかわれたよ
I was teased, being told she still has it
何にもいいこと なかったけど 葛飾水元
Nothing good ever happened, but Katsushika Mizumoto
流れる雲と ラプソディー口ずさみ 少し歩こうか
Singing a rhapsody with the floating clouds, shall we walk a bit?
カラスがなくから もう日が暮れるね
The crows are cawing, so the sun is setting
焼き鳥ほうばり ビール飲もか
Let's stuff our faces with yakitori and drink beer
トンガリ帽子の 取水塔から
From the intake tower with the pointed hat
大志を抱いて 夕陽が落ちる
With great ambition, the setting sun goes down
明日もこうして終わるんだね
Tomorrow will end just like this too, won't it?
葛飾はまた幸せだって
Katsushika is happy once again,
隠して気がついた バカな俺だから
I realized after hiding it, because I'm a fool.
どこかに元気を落っことしても
Even if I drop my energy somewhere,
葛飾亀有 あくびをひとつ
In Katsushika Kameari, I let out a yawn.
変わらない街並みが 妙に優しいよ
The unchanging cityscape is strangely kind.
アキロゼ生誕祭2026をご覧の皆さん、いかがでしたでしょうか？
To everyone watching AkiRose Birthday 2026, how did you enjoy it?
さて、ここからは大事なお知らせがあるから、最後までしっかり聞いていってね。
Now, I have some important announcements, so please listen closely until the end.
まずは、お知らせひとつ目。
First, the first announcement.
アキ・ローゼンタール2026誕生日グッズ発売です！
Aki Rosenthal 2026 Birthday Goods are now on sale!
今回はライブの世界観をぎゅっと楽しんでもらえるグッズを頑張って制作いたしました。
This time, I worked hard to create goods that let you enjoy the worldview of the live show.
なので、今回のライブが良かったなーって思った方は、ぜひ応援で購入していただくのもすごく嬉しいです。
So, if you enjoyed the show, I'd be very happy if you bought them to show your support.
それでは、まずひとつ目のグッズ。
Well then, let's look at the first item.
Life is GAME ラバーマット。
Life is GAME Rubber Mat.
今回のイラストはLAM先生に描き下ろしていただきました。素敵なイラストありがとうございます！
The illustration this time was drawn by LAM-sensei. Thank you for the wonderful illustration!
今回のライブの世界観をイメージしたイラストになっています。
The illustration is inspired by the worldview of this live performance.
めちゃくちゃセクシーで色っぽいけどカッコイイようなアキロゼになっています。
It shows an AkiRose who is incredibly sexy and alluring, yet also cool.
ラバーマットで思う存分楽しんでください。
Please enjoy it to your heart's content with this rubber mat.
ちなみにサイズはカードゲームにぴったり。この意味、わかるよね？
By the way, the size is perfect for card games. You know what that means, right?
2つ目のグッズが、運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット。
The second item is the '5 Cards of Destiny' Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set.
アキロゼがあなたのことを占って背中を押してあげます。
AkiRose will tell your fortune and give you a push forward.
1日の始まりや、何か運命を託したい…みたいなそんな時に使って楽しむ。
Enjoy using it at the start of your day, or when you want to leave something to fate.
そして5枚バーンって飾っておけるので、見ても楽しめるようになっています。
And since you can display all five together, it's also a joy to look at.
占い方法は、このあと紹介するアキロゼのASMRボイスと連動しております。
The fortune-telling method is linked with the AkiRose ASMR voice I'll introduce next.
飾っても楽しい、使っても楽しい、そのような連動グッズになっているので、ぜひゲットしてください。
It's a linked item that's fun to both display and use, so please get it.
続いてのグッズは、アキロゼのトランプ！作っちゃいました！
The next item is AkiRose playing cards! We actually made them!
こちら実際に遊んでいただけるトランプなので、たくさん予備も買ったほうがいいんじゃないかなと思います。
Since these are actual playing cards you can use, maybe it's better to buy plenty of spares.
ぜひトランプでもアキロゼをたくさん楽しんで、アピールもしてくださいね。
Please enjoy AkiRose through the cards and show them off too.
続いてはこちら。アキロゼのカードケース。
Next is this: the AkiRose Card Case.
トランプはもちろん、タロットなど小物入れても大丈夫です。
It's perfect for playing cards, of course, or for tarot cards and small accessories.
ぜひお家や持ち歩きに使ってね。
Please use it at home or when you're out and about.
そして、ボイスの紹介です。今回もASMRボイスを特別に発売！
And now for the voices. We're releasing special ASMR voices again!
アキとロゼがそれぞれ左右からあなたのことを誘惑しちゃうかも。
Aki and Rose might both try to seduce you from either side.
台本も頑張って書いたので、ぜひぜひたっぷり楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I worked hard on the script, so I hope you enjoy it to the fullest.
こちらボイスは「Life is GAME 〜アキとロゼの盤上〜」、こちらをメインとし、
The main voice is 'Life is GAME ~Aki and Rose's Game Board~',
ASMRショートボイスとして、先ほどの「運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット」と連動したショートボイスが入っております。
And as ASMR short voices, we have clips linked to the '5 Cards of Destiny' Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set.
ショートボイスのシャッフル・ランダム再生をして選ばれたボイスがあなたの運命の1枚になります。
Play the short voices on shuffle/random, and the one chosen will be your card of destiny.
ぜひいろいろ楽しんでね。
Please have fun with them in many ways.
これらのグッズすべてが詰まったフルセット購入には、なんと特典も付いております。
And for the full set which includes all these items, there's even a special bonus.
今回のキービジュアルのイラストを使ったチケット風カードになっております。
It's a ticket-style card featuring this show's key visual illustration.
あなたはこのゲームに参加する？参加しない？
Will you join this game? Or will you not?
こちらもライブの世界観を高めるアイテムになっているので、ぜひゲットしてください。
This is also an item that enhances the worldview of the live show, so please get it.
そして、数量限定あります。直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ったものになっております。頑張って書きます！
Also, there's a limited quantity version with a handwritten signature and a foil-pressed message. I'll do my best writing them!
そして数量限定が終わり次第、箔押しでの複製サインとメッセージが入ったチケット風カードになります。
Once the limited ones are gone, it'll switch to a version with a foil-pressed signature and message.
ぜひフルセット購入特典ゲットしてね。
Please make sure to get the full set purchase bonus.
大事な発売時間は、このあと21時30分。21時30分にショップオープンです。ぜひ登録など準備して備えておいてね。
The important sale time is 21:30, coming up next. The shop opens at 21:30. Please be ready with your registrations and all.
続きまして、お知らせ2つ目。
Moving on to the second announcement.
このあと21時45分からメンバー限定のアフターライブを行います！
Starting at 21:45 after this, I'll be doing a member-only after-live stream!
ライブ本編とはまた違う楽曲を披露する予定なので、ぜひお楽しみに。
I plan to perform different songs than in the main show, so please look forward to it.
今日メンバーになった方もぜひぜひ見てね。
Those who became members today, please come and watch too.
ちなみに過去のライブのメンバー限定アフターライブも見れちゃうと思うので、ぜひそちらも…。
By the way, I think you can also watch member-only after-lives from previous shows, so check those out too...
あたりも見てみてねー。
Check around too!
ちなみに、今回のサムネイルイラストは...
By the way, this time's thumbnail illustration...
...メンバー限定で壁紙としてプレゼント予定です。
...is planned to be given to members as a wallpaper.
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
そして、お知らせ3つ目！
And, the third announcement!
本日の生誕祭ライブの後も...
Even after today's birthday live...
...お楽しみはまだまだ続きます。
...the fun will continue.
なんと、ホロアースにて特別企画...
Surprisingly, a special project in Holoearth...
...「アキー・ローゼンタール生誕祭アンコール in ホロアース」...
..."Aki Rosenthal Birthday Live Encore in Holoearth"...
...を開催しまーす！
...will be held!
今回初披露した新曲『モノポリー』をホロアースで歌っちゃいます！
I'll sing the new song "Monopoly" that I performed for the first time today in Holoearth!
色んな角度からアキロゼのパフォーマンスや演出を...
Akirose's performance and production from various angles...
...じっくりと見てみてくださいね。
...please take a close look at them.
さらに、ホロアースだけのMCパートもたっぷりあるので...
Furthermore, there's plenty of MC parts only in Holoearth...
...ぜひぜひ会いに来てください！
...so please come and see me!
開催日は3月13日、3月13日です！
The date is March 13th, March 13th!
詳細はホロアース公式Xをチェックしてね！
Check the Holoearth official X for details!
そして、最後のお知らせが！
And, the final announcement!
新曲『モノポリー』！
New song, "Monopoly"!
本日日付が変わる頃にリリースされますので...
It will be released around the time the date changes today...
...各音楽配信サービスからぜひ購入してね！たくさん聴いてね！
...so please purchase it from various music distribution services! Listen to it a lot!
振付も歌もとってもキャッチーなので...
The choreography and the song are both very catchy...
...覚えてみんなで楽しんでもらえる、愛されるような楽曲になってくれたら...
...I hope it becomes a beloved song that everyone can remember and enjoy together...
...嬉しいなーって思っています。
...I'd be happy if it did.
また、後日ライブ配信で...
Also, in a later live stream...
...新曲『モノポリー』だったり、今回のライブに触れた後日談など...
...I'd like to talk about the new song "Monopoly" and behind-the-scenes stories from this live...
...語ったり、一緒に見たりなどしたいなと思っているのーで...
...and watch it together with you...
...ぜひチャンネル登録、高評価ポチ、通知もオン！
...so please subscribe to the channel, hit the like button, and turn on notifications!
し、忘れてた人は、今ポチッとしてね！
If you forgot, hit it now!
絶対絶対また会いに来てね！
Make sure to come and see me again!
それでは。
Well then.
運命は時に残酷。
Fate is sometimes cruel.
あなたが選びたくて選んだものではないかもしれない。
It may not be something you wanted to choose.
だけど、いつでもあなたの人生はあなたのもの。
But your life is always yours.
人生は一度きり。
Life is only once.
やり直しのきかないこのゲーム。
This game that cannot be redone.
あなたはどう楽しむ？
How will you enjoy it?
【主催者】 アキー・ローゼンタール
Organizer: Aki Rosenthal
【出演者】
Performers
【歌唱ゲスト】
Singing Guests
【振付制作】
Choreography Production
【バックダンサー】
Back Dancers
【サムネイルイラスト】
Thumbnail Illustration
【ロゴ制作】
Logo Production
【モノポリー ジャケットイラスト】
Monopoly Jacket Illustration
【モノポリー ジャケットロゴ】
Monopoly Jacket Logo
【音源制作】
Sound Production
【Special Thanks】
Special Thanks
2/17 21:45 Start
Life is GAME
Member Only After Live
START
END